Updates to the action bar in 2024
release wave one make it simpler to use
and make you more productive.
We've tidied up the workspace a bit.
First, there's a new icon for analysis
mode. It's in the same place and still
turns analysis mode on and off, but now
takes up less space.
We've also created space by removing the
captions for search and analysis mode.
Copilot's now on the action bar, so it's
easier to reach Copilot actions on any
list page.
Lastly, everyone can now enjoy the
updates to the action bar.
It's now standard
and the process tab is now called home.
It's where the most popular actions are.
There you'll find split buttons that
group popular actions for fast access.
To learn more, go to aka.ms/bcactionbar.
Thanks for watching.